# Mahipal Singh Choudhary

.Net | Angular Developer

I am 3 years experienced developer with a solid background in a wide range of .NET development aspects in a business application context. My expertise includes all development stages, from initial analysis through design and execution.



mschoudhary81@gmail.com 🔀

07568787918

Jodhpur, Rajasthan (India)

linkedin.com/in/mahipal-choudhary-b0290494 in

github.com/choudharymahipal 🔘

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# .Net Developer

Anand Rathi IT Pvt. Ltd. Jodhpur, Rajasthan

07/2019 - Present

ARITPL was founded by Mr. Anand Rathi. They deal in financial products related to mutual funds , shares , insurances etc.

#### Role and Responsibilities

- I am working with ASP .NET MVC with C#, Angular 11, Azure SSO, Web APIs, JavaScript & jQuery.
- Perform code reviews and ensure security and performance considerations are communicated and adhered to.
- Designs, executes, documents and makes corrections to complex programs in accordance with analysis specifications and prescribed norms.
- Manage repository on GitLab and SVN. and We are using JIRA for tracking sprint and daily basis tasks.

# Associate .Net Developer

Anand Rathi IT Pvt. Ltd. Jodhpur, Rajasthan

03/2018 - 06/2019

Role and Responsibilities

- Developing, maintaining and supporting web-based applications for corporate Intranet and application systems.
- Responsible for design, programming, deployment, testing and maintenance of one or more applications.
- Implemented new features like security, API encryption, SSO and JWT.

# **EDUCATION**

MCA with 70%

Rajasthan Technical University, Kota

07/2016 - 07/2018

# **BCA with 64.91%**

Makhanlal Chaturvedi National University of Journalism and Communication, Kota

07/2012 - 07/2015

# LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES



# **PROJECTS**

#### Benefit Plus (02/2020 - Present)

- Benefit Plus is employee benefits & wellness worries with enrolment & claims analytical reports. Through our web portal & mobile app, Employees can enjoy easy enrolment, claims tracking, search nearest network hospital and download E-card & other useful documents.
- https://benefitplus.anandrathiinsurance.com

## SSOCS (03/2018 - 06/2018)

- SSOCS is known as Shree Sanwarlal Osteopath Charitable Sansthan is a Charitable Institute. We built entire modules as a hospital management system. In this booking room, appointments, News and events etc.
- http://parasharhealing.com

#### General Insurance (05/2019 - 11/2019)

- General insurance or non-life insurance policies, including automobile and homeowners policies, provide payments depending on the loss from a particular financial event.
- http://gi.anandrathiinsurance.com

#### ARIBL (03/2020 - 06/2020)

- Anand Rathi Insurance Brokers Limited (ARIBL) is a part of the Anand Rathi Group, This is a official website of ARIT.
- https://www.anandrathiinsurance.com

#### Protection Dinamica (06/2020 - 09/2020)

- It is Goods Mediclaim project same as Benefit Plus application. This
  project have multi-language features like English and Spanish.
- https://eicuat.rathi.com/ProtectionDinamica-Live

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

.Net | Angular | JavaScript and JQuery 3 month internship From ARIT Pvt. Ltd. Jodhpur, Rajasthan. (12/2017 - 03/2018)

Quaterly Quality Award (07/2020 - 09/2020)

Best Employee Of The Quarter

# **LANGUAGES**

Hindi Native or Bilingual Proficiency English

Limited Working Proficiency

## INTERESTS

Singing

Travelling

Reading Books